Guide to the Amos Vogel Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Films, 1896-2001
  - Subseries II.3: Notebooks, 1974-1995
    - 1985
      - Unknown Festivals, 1985, (2 Folders) (Box 64, Folder 6 to 7)
    - 1986
      - New York Film Festival, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - New York University Symposium, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Socialist Scholars Conference, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Unknown Festivals, 1984-1986 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - 1987
      - New York Film Festival/Mead Festival, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Unknown festivals, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - 1988
      - Grierson, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Kluge I/New York Film Festival/Margaret Mead Festival, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Kluge II/New York Film Festival, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Kluge III/ Margaret Mead Festival, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Kluge IV, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - New York Film Festival, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Unknown Festivals, 1987-1988, (2 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 5 to 6)
    - 1989
      - MOMA, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - New Director Series, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - New York Film Festival, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Socialist Scholars Conference, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - 1990
      - [Theodores] Angelopoulos Retrospective, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - New Directors Series, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - New York Film Festival, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - 1991--Unknown Festival (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - 1992
      - New Directors Series, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - New York Film Festival--Notebooks 1 and 2, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - New York Film Festival--Notebook 3, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Unknown Festival, 1992, (2 Folders) (Box 68, Folder 4 to 5)
    - 1993
      - [Makav-], 1993 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - New York Film Festival, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - 1994--New York Film Festival (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - 1995--Unknown Festival, (2 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 2 to 3)
  - Subseries II.4: Festivals and Conferences 1934-1997
    Throughout Amos Vogel's career, he actively screened films for potential showing at Cinema 16 events, Annenberg film classes, and various lectures and talks. These films were also the potential subject matter for articles as well as inclusion in Vogel's book, Film as Subversive Art. The files in this subseries are from film festivals and conferences held within the United States and in Europe. Within the files are printed matter, such as programs and descriptions of the films and publicity material from the production company, newspaper clippings, articles from both performing arts and mainstream publications and, of course, Vogel's own copious notes. The subseries is arranged by festival or conference title and within that chronologically.
    - American Film Festival
      - 1980 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - 1981 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - 1982 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - 1983 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - 1984 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1981, (3 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 3 to 5)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1983
      - General, 1983, (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Alien Friends, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Alrune, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Ana, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Animanda, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Ariane, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - The Beautiful Prisoner, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Der Berg, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Born in Flames, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Canal Grande, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Carnival in the Dark, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Couple Regards Positions, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Danton, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Dialogue of Rome, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Dreaming Lips, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - The End, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Le Enfant Secret, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Es Ging Tag und Nacht den Ganzen, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Eureka, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Fraulein Else, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Hecate, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Heinrich Penthiselea von Kleist, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - Un Homme de la Tourment, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 24)
      - Journey to the End of the Night, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - Krieg und Frieden, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - Leuchtturm des Chaos, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 27)
      - Lisa and Suzanne, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - Nachtlied des Hundes, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - NJU, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Ortsbesichtigung von Palestina, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 31)
      - Page from Dalmasse Hotel, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 32)
      - Pauline on the Beach, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Protest Demonstrations in Israel, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 34)
      - Querelle, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - La Rabbia, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 36)
      - Real Time, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 37)
      - Shift, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 38)
      - Mit Starren Blick aufs Geld, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 39)
      - Stolen Life, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 40)
      - Sunless, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 41)
      - Symphonie, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 42)
      - Der Traumende Mund, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 43)
      - Utopia, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 44)
      - Verliebt auf Eigenen Wunsch (Love by Request), 1987 (Box 71, Folder 45)
      - Vertical Features Remake, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 46)
      - A Walk Through H, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 47)
      - Who Knocks on My Door, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 48)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1986, (4 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 1 to 4)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1987
      - General, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Alice, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Arab Cinema, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Asja's Happiness, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - The Burglar, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Cobra Verde, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - The Commissar, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - A Dead Man Visits the Living, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Family Viewing, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Hairspray, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Heimkehr, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - The Journey, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Das Jüngste Gericht, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - The Lit Lantern, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Missile, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - The Non-Professionals, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Notebooks, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - The Soul of Money, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Robinsons Garden, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - The Theme, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Vater's Land, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1988
      - General, 1988, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 18 to 19)
      - Arabesques on Pirosmani, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Beginning of an Unknown Century, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Beirut: The Last Home Movie, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Bell Diamond, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Dogura Magura, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Forward, Army of God, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Friendship's Death, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - The Houses Are Full of Smoke, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - In Georgia, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Keep Your Right Up, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Klimov, [198-] (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Last of England, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - The Man with Three Coffins, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - Manifesto of the Fools, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Plain Talk and Common Sense, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Rorret, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - Satyajit Ray, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 15)
      - Andrej Tarkowskijs Exil un Tod, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 16)
      - Wohin? Achternbusch, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - Yeelen, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1989
      - General, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 74, Folder 19 to 20)
      - Notebooks, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 21)
      - Notebooks, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1990, (3 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 2 to 4)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1991
      - General, 1991, (2 Folders) (Box 75, Folder 5 to 6)
      - General, 1991, (2 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Notebooks, 1991, (2 Folders) (Box 76, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1992
      - General, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - General, 1992, (3 Folders) (Box 77, Folder 1 to 3)
      - Befreier und Befreite, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Begotten, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Brüder und Schwestern, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Erinnern und Vergessen, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Die Gätern des Skorpions, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Gas, Food, Lodging, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Good Woman of Bangkok, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Identifikation der Wünsche, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Latest News about Doomsday, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Das Leben der Bohème, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Lessons in Darkness, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Man Without a World, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - The Migrants, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - Notebooks, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - Rimbaud, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - Rostige Bilder, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - Scream of Stone, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 20)
      - Skinless Night, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 21)
      - Soll Sein, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 22)
      - Suspicion, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 23)
      - A Winter's Tale, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 24)
      - Yiddle with His Fiddle, 1936 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1993 (Vogel Did Not Attend) (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1994
      - General, 1994, (4 Folders) (Box 78, Folder 2 to 5)
      - Notebooks, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Berlin Film Festival 1995
      - General, 1995, (3 Folders) (Box 79, Folder 2 to 4)
      - Notebooks, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Berlin Film Festival, 1997 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Cannes 1988
      - General, 1988, (2 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Notebooks, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Clermont-Ferrond, 1994, (2 Folders) (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Copenhagen Film + Video Festival, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - EFLA, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - EFLA, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Glasnost Film Festival 1989
      - General, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Adonis XIV, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - African Hunt, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Against the Current, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - And the Past Seems But a Dream, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Assa, [1980s] (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Aura, [1980s] (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - The Bam Zone, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Black Square, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Chernobyl: Chronicle of Difficult Weeks, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Countersuit, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Days of Darkness, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Dialogues, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Early on Sunday, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - Elegia and Abendoffer, 1984-1987 (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - Evening Sacrifice, 1984-1987 (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Final Verdict, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - Group of Comrades, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 19)
      - Homecoming, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 20)
      - Little Vera, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - The Lonely Voice of the Man, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 22)
      - Maria, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 23)
      - Marshal Blücher, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 24)
      - My Friend Ivan Lapshin, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 25)
      - The Needle, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 26)
      - Risk I, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 27)
      - Risk II, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 28)
      - Rok, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 29)
      - Scenes at a Fountain, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 30)
      - The Servant (Sluga), 1988 (Box 81, Folder 31)
      - Solovki Power, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 32)
      - The Tailor, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 33)
      - Ten Minutes Older, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 34)
      - Theatre Square, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 35)
      - This Is How We Live, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 36)
      - Tomorrow Is a Holiday, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 37)
      - The Trial, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 38)
      - The Wood Goblin, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 39)
    - Holland Festival, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 40)
    - Independent Film Festival 1991 (Box 81, Folder 41)
    - The Jewish Museum, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Margaret Mead Film Festival, 1987-1988 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Museum of Modern Art
      - Academy Program of Documentaries, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - "Comedy, Italian Style," 1986 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Russian Films, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - The Neighborhood Film Project, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - New Directors, New Films
      - 1982 April (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - 1987 March (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - 1988 March (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - 1992 March-April (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - 2000 March-April (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - New York Film Festival
      - 1977 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - 1979 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - 1980 (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - 1987 (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - 1989 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - 1990 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - 1991 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - 1993 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - 1994 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - 1997 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - The New York Institute for the Humanities--"Film as False Sociology," 1979 October (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - New York Video Festival, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Oberhausen, 1994
      - General, 1994, (2 Folders) (Box 83, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Notebooks, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Odense Film Festival, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Odense Film Festival--General, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Odense Film Festival--Notebooks, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Paris Film Festival, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Pesaro Film Festival, 1991
      - General, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Notebooks, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Subversive Film Festival, 1992
      - General, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Article by Amos Vogel, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Articles, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - Un Chien Delicieux, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - The Creation of Life, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - Cyberpunk, 1990 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - Delusions of Self-Immolation, [1990] (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Documents Interdits I-II, [1990] (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - Homoparadoksum, 1989-1990 (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - Inside Iraq, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Leeches and Fleeces, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Linda/Les & Annie, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Mistress of the Rings, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Motorway, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - My Way, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Planetens Spejle, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Printed Material, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Shooting Script, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - Stigmata, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 10)
      - Subtitle, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - Time Code Selection, undated (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - The Will to Provoke, undated (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - Workshop Update, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 14)
      - Zygosis, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Temple University--"Conference on Culture and Communication," 1981 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Unknown Film Festivals
      - Achieving Sexual Maturity, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 17)
      - America the Beautiful, undated (Box 85, Folder 18)
      - The Art of Seeing with One's Own Eyes, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 19)
      - Asparagus, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 20)
      - Attack on the Americas, 1972-1981 (Box 85, Folder 21)
      - The Battle of Algiers, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 22)
      - Dear Friends, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 23)
      - Demonstrations in Perception, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 24)
      - Desire Pie, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 25)
      - Dressed to Kill, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 26)
      - Drums Along the Mohawk, 1939 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Eclipse, 1962, 1981, (2 Folders) (Box 86, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Erogeny, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Frontline, 1980-1982 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Gender, [1978] (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Going Places, 1948 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Hardware Wars, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Holding, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - La Hora de los Hornos, 1967-1969 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - How the Myth Was Made, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - I Am Curious, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - Inside Cackle Corners, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - Introduction to Visual Illusions, undated (Box 86, Folder 14)
      - Junior High, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 15)
      - La, La, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 16)
      - Make Mine Freedom, [1948] (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - Man of Aran, 1934 (Box 86, Folder 18)
      - Masculine-Feminine, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 19)
      - Meet King Joe, 1951 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - The Miracle, 1948 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Notorious, 1946 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Only the Strong, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Particle Removal Series, 1972-1973 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Payment of Teresa Videla, [1980s] (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Phi Phenomenon, [1982] (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - A Quickie, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Responding, undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - The Rest of Your Life, 1972-1986 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - River Body, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - Rosie the Riveter, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - Self-Loving, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Shadow of Doubt, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - So Is This, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Sun Children, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - The 30-Second Dream, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - Truthfully Speaking, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - Unconscious Motivation, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - The War Game, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - Ways of Seeing, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 21)
      - The Whole Film, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 22)
      - Why Vietnam, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 23)
      - Words of Love, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - Viennale, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - Viennale, 1993-1994
      - General, 1993-1994 (Box 87, Folder 26)
      - General, 1993-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 88, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Article, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 88, Folder 3 to 4)
      - Austrian Resistance Archive, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Avant-Garde Filmmakers, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Avant-Garde Filmmakers, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 89, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Non Avant-Garde Filmmakers, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 89, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Viennale, 1994-1996 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Subseries II.5: Subject Files, 1947-2001
    This subseries holds topical files. The majority of the subseries consists of poop sheets and printed material for films that Amos Vogel screened. There is also a large amount of documents in regards to Vogel's work as co-founder and director of the Lincoln Center Film Festival from the early 1960s until the early 1970s. Held in this series is correspondence with friends and colleagues spanning from about the mid-1970s until the 2000s. Notable individuals include Werner Herzog, "Weegee," and Jonas Mekas.
    - American Writers Congress, 1981 October (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - American Film Institute
      - General, 1967-1976 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Award, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Anger, Kenneth, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Ann Arbor Films, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Anthology Film Archives, 1966-1975 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Antonioni, Michelangelo, [1980s] (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Amos Vogel Series, 1994-1997 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Austrian Cultural Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Austrian Films--General, 1995, (2 Folders) (Box 90, Folder 9 to 10)
    - Austrian Films--Austrian Culture Exodus Conference, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - "Bergman and Dreams," 1978 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - "Best" Films, 1977-1978 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Best United States Independent Features, undated, 1979 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Bienstock, David, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Borin, Ann, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Brakhage, Stan, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - The Brothers Quay, 1986-1987 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Canby, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Cargnelli, Christian, 1998-2002 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Cinema 16
      - Distribution Contracts, 1965-1967, (2 Folders) (Box 91, Folder 8 to 9)
      - Tributes--Film Forum, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Tributes--Museum of Modern Art, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Cinematic First, undated (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Committee on Film and Television Resources, 1973-1976, (2 Folders) (Box 91, Folder 13 to 14)
    - Community Media Project, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 2)
        - 1974 (Box 92, Folder 3)
        - 1975, (2 Folders) (Box 92, Folder 4 to 5)
        - 1976 (Box 92, Folder 6)
        - 1977 (Box 92, Folder 7)
        - 1978-1980 (Box 92, Folder 8)
        - 1993-1995 (Box 93, Folder 1)
        - 1996-2001 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Herzog, Werner, 1976-1977, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Heskowitz, Richard, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Loomis, Robert, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Mekas, Jonas, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - "VIP," 1947-1962 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - "Weegee," 1947-1952 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Crawdaddy, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Cultural Environmental Movement, 1993-1996 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Distributors, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - De Capua, Michael, 2001 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Diener, Mick, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Documentary Film Week, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Dratfield Endowment, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Fassbinder, Rainer Werner, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Festival of the Arts, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - "Film as Art"--Port Washington Library, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - "Film as Art"--Walnut Street Theatre Talk, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Films in New York
      - 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - 1987 Winter (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - 1988 Fall, (2 Folders) (Box 94, Folder 7 to 8)
      - 1988 Spring (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Flat Film Master List, 1979-1981 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Foreman, Richard, 1976-1979 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Forman, Milos (BAM Appearance), 2000 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Gandert, Gero, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - German Books, 1992-1994 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Greaves, William, 1991-1992 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Grove Press, undated, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Horak, Jan-Christopher, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Jump-Cut, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Kaplan, Jo Anne, 1985-1987 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Leigh, Mike, 1992 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Lincoln Center
      - Benefit Story, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Chaplin, Charles, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Letters to the Editors, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - New York Film Festival, 1963-1972, (2 Folders) (Box 95, Folder 11 to 12)
      - New York Times, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Newsweek Article, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - Resignation, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - Sontag, Susan, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - Variety, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - "Very Important," 1964-1969 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Mailer, Norman, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Margaret Mead Festival, 1992 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Master Film Files
      - General, 1963-1978, (3 Folders) (Box 96, Folder 5 to 7)
      - Cinema 16, 1959-1962 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Cinema 16, 1959-1962 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - [Mellen], J., undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Micro-Analysis Methodology, [1980s] (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - "More Light," 1988 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - The Museum of Broadcasting, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - New York Film Festival, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Northwest Film Festival (Portland), 1980 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Notebooks, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Notes, undated, 1971-1986, (2 Folders) (Box 97, Folder 9 to 10)
    - Poop Sheets
      - 1977 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - 1978, (2 Folders) (Box 98, Folder 2 to 3)